Guide to the Sterling Memorial Library, Yale University, Photographs of Windows
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Sterling Memorial Library, Yale University, photographs of windows
1995-1998
RU 392
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
4.75
The materials consist of photographs documenting the decorative windows in the Sterling Memorial Library at Yale, with an emphasis on the main reading room and the stack tower.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-B (YRG 46-B), Records and materials documenting individual Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of photographs documenting the decorative windows in the Sterling Memorial Library at Yale, with an emphasis on the main reading room and the stack tower.
Academic libraries; College buildings; Photographs; Yale University -- Pictorial works; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University. Library
- Photographs, 1995-1996; Accession 1996-A-065
  - Roll #1, sixth floor office stacks, 1996 January 07 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Roll #2, office stacks, 1996 January 07 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Roll #3, fifth floor office stacks, 1996 January 07 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Roll #4, fourth floor, 1996 January 07 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Roll #5-#8, stacks, 1996 January 07 (Box 1, Folder 5 - 8)
  - Roll #9, stacks, 1996 February 08 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Roll #13-#18, stacks full views, 1996 February 08 (Box 1, Folder 10 - 15)
  - Roll #19, office stacks full views, 1996 March 05 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Roll #20-#23 [includes #20A], office stacks, 1996 March 05 (Box 1, Folder 17 - 21)
  - Roll #24-#25, exhibit corridor, 1996 March 05 (Box 1, Folder 22 - 23)
  - Roll #26, stacks full views, 1996 March 05 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Roll #27, office stacks full views, 1996 March 05 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Roll #28, fifth floor office stacks full view/unlit, 1996 March 05 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Roll #29, office stacks, unlit fourth floor full views, 1996 March 05 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Roll #30, office stacks full views, 1996 March 05 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Roll #31, office stacks full views and medallions, 1996 March 05 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Roll #32, 5S office stacks, 1996 March 05 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Roll #33-#34, sixth floor office stacks, 1996 March 05 (Box 1, Folder 31 - 32)
  - Roll #35, fifth and sixth floor office stacks, 1996 March 05 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Roll #36, fourth and fifth floor office stacks, 1996 March 05 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Roll #37, fourth floor office stacks medallions, 1996 March 05 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Roll #38, fourth floor and seventh floor full view stacks, Memorabilia Room, 1996 March 05 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Roll #39, seventh floor office stacks full viewa, 1996 March 05 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Roll #40, seventh floor office stacks medallions, 1996 March 06 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Roll #41, seventh floor office stacks full views and medallions, 1996 March 06 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Roll #42, seventh floor office stacks full views, 1996 March 06 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Roll #43, seventh floor office stacks full views lit, 1996 March 06 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Roll #44, fifth floor and sixth floor stacks full views and medallions, 1996 March 06 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Roll #45, office stacks full views and medallions, 1996 March 06 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Roll #46, seventh floor office stacks, 1996 March 06 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Roll #1M-#3M, Memorabilia Room full views and medallions, 1996 March 06 (Box 1, Folder 45 - 47)
  - Roll #4M, Memorabilia Room medallions, 1996 March 06 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Roll #5M-#6M, Memorabilia Room full views and medallions, 1996 March 06 (Box 1, Folder 49 - 50)
  - Roll #C-9, frames 00A-12A, 1996 March 06 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Roll #7M, Memorabilia Room full views and medallions, 1996 March 06 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Roll #C-8, Rooms 135, 138, 406 full views and medallions, 1996 March 06 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Roll #C-9, frames 13A-35A, 1996 March 06 (Box 1, Folder 54 - 55)
  - Roll #C-10, 1996 March 06 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Roll #1-#2, MRR, 1995 December 15 (Box 2, Folder 57 - 58)
  - Roll #3-#4, MRR medallions, 1995 December 15 (Box 2, Folder 59 - 60)
  - Roll #5, MRR, 1995 December 15 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Roll #6-#10, MRR, 1995 December 19 (Box 2, Folder 62 - 66)
  - Roll #11, MRR, 1995 December 21 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Roll #12, MRR, 1996 December 2 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Roll #13, MRR full views, 1996 December 2 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Roll #13A, MRR, 1996 March 11 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Roll #14, MRR full views, 1996 January 22 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Roll #15, MRR, 1996 January 2 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Roll #16, MRR, 1996 January 3 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Roll #17, MRR, 1996 January 4 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Roll #18-#20, MRR, 1996 January 5 (Box 2, Folder 75 - 77)
  - Roll #C-5, MRR, 1996 January 7 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Roll #21, MRR, 1996 January 12 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Roll #22, MRR, 1996 January 19 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Roll #22, MRR rejects, 1996 January 7 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Sm painted pcs rejects MRR, 1996 January 7 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Roll #C-1, MRR rejects, 1996 January 7 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Roll #C-3, MRR, 1996 January 7 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Roll #C-6, MRR, 1996 January 7 (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Photographs, 1996-1997; Accession 1999-A-061
  - Stack tower windows
    - Fourth and fifth floor, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Sixth floor, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Seventh floor, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Main Reading Room, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 4 - 6)
  - Main Reading Room, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)